24小时
第三季  第16集
前情提要
怎么回事 雪莉?
What happened, Sherry?
我进去和朱莉娅说话 艾伦打断了我们
I went to the house to speak to Julia. Alan interrupted us.
我们吵了起来 他心脏病犯了
There was an argument, and he had a heart attack.
你就这么眼睁睁看着他死去?
You stood there and you watched a man die?
解决麻烦往往只需要最简单的方法 韦恩
Complex problems sometimes have the simplest solutions, Wayne.
雪莉 这件事瞒不住的
Sherry, we can't cover this thing up.
不行也得行
We can and we will.
说好一次性付清的
The deal was we get paid in full.
因为你去了趟墨西哥 情况有变了
The deal changed when you went down to Mexico.
搞定那酒店 你会拿到剩余的钱
After you have hit the hotel, you'll get the rest of your money.
病毒在哪 你这狗娘养的
Where's the virus, you son of a bitch.
太晚了 杰克
You are too late, Jack
抓到阿马多尔了
We've got Amador
那病毒呢?
What about the virus?
我知道他们可能袭击的目标了
I think we've got a high probability target.
哪里?
What is it?
威尔希尔大街的钱德勒 广场酒店
The Chandler Plaza Hotel on Wilshire Blvd.
有什么能效劳的?
How can I help you?
有人要袭击你们酒店
There's been a threat made against your hotel.
现在是关键时刻 你必须封锁酒店不让任何人出入
As of this moment it's very important you not allow anybody in or out of the structure.
什么样的袭击?
What's the nature of the threat?
在酒店里释放传染性物质
The release of an infectious substance inside the hotel.
如果病毒扩散 你活不了 其他人也一样
If this virus gets out, you die, just like everyone else.
盖尔 病毒在中央通风系统里
Gael, the virus is in the central ventilation unit.
以下事件发生于凌晨4点至5点之间
The following takes place between 4:00 am and 5:00 am.
菲利普斯先生 我是奥尔特加探员
Mr Phillips, this is Agent Ortega
毒气已经被释放到排气系统里了
The toxic substance has been released into the forced air unit.
天哪
My god.
必须把这里封闭
You need to shut down the unit.
空气调节控制板在哪?
where is the air conditioning control panel?
在你左手边 控制板的右边
On your left, there is a row of fuses
有一排开关 每个开关对应一层楼
running down the right side of the panel one for each floor.
这些扩散了的毒气有多大危害?
Look, this toxic release, how bad is it?
奥特加探员?
Agent Orgega?
现在只能去预防 菲利普斯先生
We are just taking precautions, Mr Phillips.
你们释放了多少毒气?
How much of the virus was released?
足以让整栋楼的人丧命
Enough to kill everyone in the building.
其他地方还有没有?
Did you plant vials anywhere else?
你还不明白吗 我们都会死的
Don't you get it, we are all going to die.
其他地方还有没有?
Did you plant any other vials?
我的任务只是搞定这个酒店
My assignment was the hotel.
这么说还有别的目标
So there are others.
对
Yes.
多少?
How many?
11个 但我不知道在哪
11, but I don't know where they are.
看着他
Keep an eye on him.
德斯勒
Dessler.
米歇尔 情况怎么样?
Michelle, what's the status?
阿尔弗斯在通风系统里放了装有科迪利亚病毒的瓶子
Alvers planted a vial containing the cordilla virus in the ventilation system.
还带有定时装置
It was on a timing device.
盖尔试图解除的时候 病毒释放了
It went off as Gael was trying to disarm it.
他直接接触到了?
He was in direct contact?
对
Yeah,
他已经封锁了系统
he's shutting down the system now,
但我们得考虑到毒气可能已经渗入整座大厦
but we have to assume it's permeated the entire building.
米歇尔 接触到病毒的人
Michelle, within 14 hours,
在14小时内会出现症状
anybody exposed to the virus will become symptomatic.
还会传染到接触的人
They'll infect whoever they come in contact with.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
一个人也不能从这离开
No one can be allowed to leave the building.
必须实施全封闭隔离
We have to impose a total quarantine.
我们会派第六分队包围那里
We will scramble a code 6 perimeter.
我们必须得谨慎 托尼
We have to be careful about this, Tony
如果里面的人知道了怎么回事 会引发大范围恐慌的
If these people realize what's going on, there will be widespread panic.
好吧 我会在100码外布置人手
All right, our people will hold a hundred yard radius,
并保持隐蔽
and stay out of sight.
洛杉矶警察局和卫生署的人会进驻酒店
Then LAPD and Health Services will move in adjacent to the hotel.
好
Good,
阿尔弗斯说还有11个类似装置
the vial that Alvers planted, he said there were 11 more
阿尔弗斯告诉你的?
Alvers told you this?
我刚见过他
I just left him.
你刚见过他? 米歇尔...
You just left him? Michelle...
他可能也接触了病毒
He could have been exposed to the virus.
他怎么离开酒店的?
How'd he get outside the hotel?
米歇尔?
Michelle?
他没离开
He didn't leave the hotel.
他还在地下室里
He is still in the basement.
你也在?
Are you inside?
对
Yeah.
你在那搞什么名堂?
What the hell are you doing in there?
我不是想当英雄 托尼
I wasn't trying to be a hero, Tony,
我只能这么做
That's the only decision I can make.
你离通风间有多远?
How far away you from the ventilation room?
不太清楚
I am not sure.
卫生署的人带了防护衣
Health service is bringing protect gear,
他们一到 你就要穿上
I want you to put it on as soon as they get there.
如果他们把你带出酒店...
Now if they get you outside of the hotel...
托尼 托尼 我不会离开的
Tony, Tony, I can't leave.
你没听见吗? 我命令你出来
Are you listening to me? I am ordering you to get out.
这个命令我不能服从
But that's the order I can't obey,
包括盖尔在内 只剩下7名探员了
as it is there are only 7 agents including Gael
酒店里全是需要控制的人
and the hotel's full of people that need to be contained and controlled,
通信 检疫都需要有人协调
Communications, testing procedures, they all have to be coordinated.
我是负责人
And I am the ranking officer
米歇尔, 听着
Michelle
我已经接触过病毒 谁也帮不了忙
I have been exposed, there is nothing anyone can do.
阿尔弗斯说还有11管病毒
Alvers said there were 11 more vials,
他说不知道在哪 我觉得他没撒谎
he said he doesn't know where they are. I believe him.
托尼?
Tony?
嗯
Yeah.
我得挂了
I have to go.
计划周详后给我电话
Call me when you have a working protocol.
让我们单独待会好吗?
Can I have a moment alone?
你我都清楚时间不多了
You and I both know I don't have a lot of time here.
我想知道你在为谁卖命 谁是主谋?
I need to know who you're working for. Who is behind this?
你说他认识我 告诉我是谁
You said he knows me, just give me a name.
随你处置
Do what you want to me.
我什么也不会说
I am telling you nothing.
我们在隔壁找到了病毒的培养皿
We found the incubator with the virus in the room next door.
如果你不招
If you don't tell me what I need to know,
我就把你放到那 然后打开它
I will put you in there and I will open it up.
那我就会死 但我还是不会说
Then I will die, but I won't talk.
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
杰克 我是查佩尔
Jack, this is Chappelle
病毒已经被释放到钱德勒 广场酒店的通风系统里了
The virus has been released into the ventilation system of the Chandler Plaza Hotel.
阿尔弗斯说还有11个 但他说不知道在哪
Alvers says there are 11 other vials, but won't or can't tell us where they are.
阿马多尔是我们唯一的线索 杰克
Amador is our only other link, Jack.
他说主谋认识我 可他不敢说出来
He says whoever's behind this knows me, but he is too afraid to give me a name.
是你共事过的还是对头?
Is it someone you worked with or against?
这也正是我想知道的
That's what we're trying to figure out.
把阿马多尔带回反恐组
Bring Amador back to CTU.
瑞恩 没时间了
Ryan, we don't have time for that.
不知道那11瓶病毒什么时候会被释放
We don't know when the 11 other vials are going to be released.
我们把他交给理查兹
We'll put him in a room with Richards.
你曾把尼娜交给理查兹
You put Nina in a room with Richards.
结果一无所获还损失了三名探员
You got no information and 3 dead agents.
瑞恩 让我来处理吧
Ryan, please, you are gonna have to let me handle this.
你得相信我
You're gonna have to trust me.
好吧
All right.
杰克
Jack.
培养皿的分析结果出来了
We've got some readings of the incubator.
刚才是瑞恩
That was Ryan.
病毒已经在钱德勒 广场酒店释放了
The virus has been released at the Chandler Plaza Hotel.
还有11瓶
There are 11 other vials,
我们还没查出在哪
we don't know where they are,
也不知道何时会被释放
and we don't know when they are gonna be released.
他可能知道
Well, he probably does.
他说他宁死也不说 我看像真的
He says he'd rather be dead than talk, and I believe him.
其实只要能抓到他的老板 就没什么好担心的
It's not going to matter though. As soon as we have his boss in custody,
他会被转作证人
we turn him over as a witness.
你在做白日梦吗 杰克?
Always thinking, aren't you, Jack?
闭嘴 面朝墙
Shut up. Take the wall.
跪下
Knees.
我们一会就回来
We'll be right back.
这些粉末被磨的非常细 足以悬浮在空中
The powder was grinded into particles, small enough to suspend it in the air.
像浮尘一样
It's like an aerosol.
钱德勒 广场酒店的窗户几乎都是关着的
Well, most of the windows at the Chandler Plaza Hotel don't open,
这也意味着被污染的空气将在酒店内部循环流动
which means the contaminated air will just circulate within the hotel.
还能控制住
We can contain it.
托尼 我是妮可·邓肯
Tony, it's Nicole Duncan.
你在去酒店的路上吗?
Are you on your way to the hotel?
对 我们正在收拾装备
Yeah, we're loading up now.
我们会尽快赶到
We'll be there as fast as we can.
你的人安排好了么?
What's the status of your people?
他们正在设置隐蔽的警戒区
They are setting up a covert perimeter.
好 我们带上移动检测仪来给酒店内的人检测
Ok, we are bringing a mobile lab to test the people inside the hotel.
但里面不能乱 否则很难完成
But that can only be accomplished if the situation is stable.
行 米歇尔会协助你们
Yeah, Michelle has got that covered.
她在酒店里? 没有任何保护?
She is inside the hotel? Unprotected?
对
Yeah.
听着 我待会打给你
Look, I will get back to you.
我们初步决定 对酒店实施全封闭隔离
Here is the protocol: total containment inside the hotel.
任何人不能离开 也不能和外界接触
No one is allowed to leave or communicate with the outside.
卫生署会设置一个警戒区
Health services will establish an adjacent perimeter.
一确认安全 洛杉矶警局的人就会进去
LAPD will move in as soon as the area is deemed safe.
好
All right.
假如有人试图离开酒店
Have they been given degree of force parameters
你有没有制定应急方案?
in case someone tries to leave the hotel?
没 你来决定吧
No, that's your call.
只要有一个人出来
One person gets out, it could start a ripple effect of disease
疾病就可能蔓延到整个城市
transmission throughout the city.
擅自闯出者 格杀勿论
Orders are shoot to kill anyone who attempts to leave.
不容有失
No exceptions.
米歇尔 所有出口都有人把守了
Michelle, all the exits have been secured.
好 我们要关闭所有电梯和通讯系统
Ok, we need to shut down the elevators and the phone system.
有这么严重吗?
It's that serious?
很可能是的
Potentially, yes.
从现在开始 谁也不能踏出酒店一步
For now, no one can leave the building.
我们的首要任务是防止造成恐慌
Our first priority is to prevent a panic.
停止酒店的运作 恐怕会引发骚乱
Shutting down hotel operations, that will create one,
而且人人都有手机
and people still have their cell phones.
我们正对酒店进行信号干扰
We're directing a jamming signal at the hotel.
那你如何和反恐组保持联系?
How do you stay in contact with CTU if the cell phones are jammed?
我们的通信使用另一种频率 不会被干扰
Our phones operate on pinhole frequency, we won't be affected.
会有人生还吗?
Is anyone going to survive this?
我们会尽最大努力
That's what we're here to ensure.
听着 菲利普斯先生 我们还要仰仗你的指挥
Look, we're going to rely on your leadership, Mr Phillips.
你和你的员工是我们的第一道防线
You and your employees will be our first line of defense.
好吗?
Ok?
我们还得关闭消防警报
We also need to shut down the fire alarm.
没有集控开关 只能一个一个的关闭
It's hardwired to the main grid. It has to be shut down one node at a time.
我来搞定吧
I will take care of it.
谢谢
Thank you.
在人们发觉之前 我们大概还有1个小时的时间
We have probably got an hour or so before people start waking up.
阿尔弗斯在哪?
Where is Alvers?
和皮特森在楼下
He's downstairs with Peterson.
除了告诉我们别处还有毒气瓶 他什么也没招
He gave up nothing except that there are more vials somewhere.
盖尔
Gael,
我知道 如果不是为了我 你也不会接触病毒
I know you wouldn't have been exposed to the virus if it wasn't for me.
你没逼我们执行任何我们完成不了的任务
You didn't have us do anything we wouldn't have done on our own.
马戈利斯?
Margolis?
嘿 稍微等会再走
Hey, I am going to need you to stay for a while.
我不能再加班了 我妻子等了我一个星期了
I can't put in OT, my wife is a week overdue.
听着 通风系统里可能混有刺激物
Oh, listen, the ventilation system may have released an irritant into the air,
我需要人帮忙 以防客人有不良反应
and I need all available personnel to deal with the guests in case there is any reaction.
我又不是医生 能帮什么忙?
I am not a doctor. What can I do?
卫生署的人正在过来的路上
The health department people they are on their way,
我保证尽快让你离开
and I promise I will get you out of here as soon as I can.
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
爸爸 是我 阿马多尔逃出大楼了
Dad, it's me. Amador has left the building.
往哪个方向跑的?
Which way is he headed?
稍等 我正在定位
Hang on, I am triangulating him now.
我们走 快点 金
We are on. Hurry, Kim.
找到了 他在西环线的16号公路路口 正向南移动
I got him. He is heading south on western and 16th.
好 我们这就出发
Ok, we are on our way.
酒店里有多少人?
How many people in the hotel?
一千左右吧
About a thousand.
给州长打电话
All right, call the governor.
如果这事泄露出去
If this thing spreads,
全市都会人心惶惶
and there is a citywide panic,
他得先准备好调动州警
he needs to be ready to mobilize the state troopers
和国家警卫队
and the national guard
是 总统先生
Yes, Mr President.
但是 告诉他
But,
没我的命令 不准轻举妄动
I want him to hold off the order until he hears from us.
是
Ok
-对不起  -嗨
-Sorry.  -Hi.
你看起来很疲惫
You look tired.
大卫 我给你带来了个麻烦 同时也有解决方法
David, I am bringing you a problem, but I'm also bringing you a solution.
先说麻烦
Let's hear the problem.
朱莉娅 米利肯
Julia Milliken.
她正被警察讯问有关艾伦的死
She was interviewed by the police about Alan's death,
而且声称我和这事有关
and she is claiming I had something to do with it.
实际上呢?
Did you?
这重要吗?
Does that really matter?
只有你才会说不重要 雪莉
Only you could say that, Sherry.
你总是说要看到真相
You know, you always claim to want the truth,
但你一生中 周围都是我和韦恩这样
but your whole life, you've been surrounded by people like me
尽力避免你被所谓真相伤害的人
and Wayne who have protected you from it.
我从未要求你们这样
I never asked to be protected.
也许是这样 但事实就是这样
Well, that may be true, but the fact remains you have been.
好吧 今晚
Well, tonight
我就如你所愿
I am going to take you at your word.
我告诉你真相
I am actually going to tell you the truth.
谢谢
Thank you.
艾伦心脏病犯的时候 我正和朱莉娅 米利肯在一起
I was with Julia Milliken when Alan had his heart attack.
她要给他药 我阻止了她
She was going to give him his medicine, and I stopped her.
我们看着他死去
We both watched him die.
这是谋杀
That's murder.
朱莉娅不能守口如瓶
And Julia couldn't keep her mouth shut.
她告诉了警察一切
She told the police everything.
警察刚才打我电话 我告诉他们
They just called me a little while ago, and I told them,
我告诉他们艾伦死的时候 我正和你在一起
I told them that I was with you at the time of Alan's death.
我猜他们不久就会向你核实
So I expect they'll be contacting you to verify my story.
你希望我帮你圆谎?
And you expect me to do that?
哦 大卫 你不帮我就犯了严重错误
Oh, David, it would be a serious mistake not to.
因为你要是不这么做 我就告诉他们我是为了你的利益
Because if you don't, I will tell them that I was acting on your behalf.
没人会相信我让你去杀艾伦·米利肯
No one's gonna believe that I asked you to kill Alan Milliken.
对
No.
但也许他们相信你和他有过节
But maybe they'll believe that you were having a problem with him,
曾告诉我采取一切必要措施解决他
that you told me to take all necessary measures to solve it.
对媒体来说 这可是颗重磅炸弹 你觉得呢?
Now, that's a nice sound bite for the media, don't you think?
采取一切必要措施?
Take all necessary measures?
我从未说过这样的话
I never used those words.
那好
Well.
你考虑清楚 大卫
Think it over, David.
好了 托尼 我接通你了
Ok, Tony, I have got you on speaker.
我们在胡佛大道上向南开 就是阿马多尔所在的佛蒙特大道的平行道上
We are on Hoover headed south running parallel to Amador's position on Vermont.
嗯 找到你们俩了
Yeah, we've got you both.
你的频率收发器放在哪了?
Where did you put the transponder?
他手上的绷带上
In the bandage on his hand.
你搞不好会鸡飞蛋打 杰克
You know, this could all backfire, Jack.
我们别无选择 我们得让他相信他逃了出来
We didn't have a choice, we had to let him believe that he had escaped.
我的意思是你费劲心思地跟踪他
I am just saying that while you are tied up following him,
他可能只是想逃出城
he may just be heading out of town.
不 阿马多尔的老板门路很多
No, whoever Amador's working for has got connections all around the world.
要离开这肯定会找他帮忙
He's gonna need his help to get out of here.
需要支援吗?
You want some backup?
不用 路上车子不多
No. There's not very many cars on the road.
再靠近的话 他会发现的
If we get any closer, he'll make us.
对了 米歇尔有没有整理出这5年内我接触过的人的名单?
Look, did Michelle compile the list of all the contacts I have had over the last 5 years?
我让克萝伊去办
Look, I had to put Chloe on it.
米歇尔现在在钱德勒 广场酒店里
Michelle's inside the Chandler Plaza Hotel.
很抱歉 托尼
I am sorry, Tony.
听着 我们发现病毒已经被处理过了
Look, we think the virus has been altered.
怎么处理的?
Altered how?
和别的化学物质结合在一起
It was combined with another chemical.
现在已经送往卫生部检测了
It's on its way over to NHS to get tested now.
你意思是她还有生还机会
So you are saying she might have a chance.
也许 希望如此
Maybe, I hope so.
听着 托尼 一有消息我就通知你 好吗?
Look, Tony, we'll get back to you as soon as we have got anything, ok?
喂?
Yes?
我是阿马多尔
It's Amador.
我刚才被反恐局的什么探员抓住了
I was detained by some CTU agents.
他们对我严刑逼供 想让我把你供出来
They put me through hell, trying to force me to give you up.
那你招了吗?
Did you?
当然没有
Of course not.
我得离开这里
I need a way out of the country.
行
Of course.
抓你的人里有杰克·鲍尔吗?
Was Jack Bauer one of the agents?
有
Yes.
先确保你没被跟踪 然后我们再见面
I need you to be certain you are not being followed before we meet.
你知道该怎么做吧
You know what to do.
明白
Understood.
好
Good
好了打我电话
Call me when you are sure.
知道位置了吧?
You have the location?
你想什么时候行动?
When do you want it released?
这个电话第二次响的时候
This will ring twice.
调好计时器后 记得弄坏它
Once you set the timer, make sure it's destroyed.
你还要多久能到?
How long before you can move in?
半小时
About half an hour.
我们发现病毒被处理过了 和另一种化合物结合在一起
We found out that the virus was altered, combined with another compound.
嗯 在分析结果出来之前 我们也不知道会怎么样
Yeah, well, until that compound's analyzed, we have no idea what we're dealing with.
接触到病毒的人死亡率有多高?
So, what's the mortality rate among those exposed to the virus?
假如是原形态 接近90%
In its unaltered form, approximately 90%.
那 假如...
Look, if...
假如只接触病毒片刻
if somebody was exposed for just a short time,
马上离开酒店会不同吗?
would leaving the hotel make a difference?
我意思是... 我知道这是无稽之谈 但...
I mean... I know I am not making sense here, but...
接触了就是接触了
Once you are exposed, you are exposed.
接触时间长短和存活率无关
The length of exposure has no real bearing on survivability.
好吧 听着
All right, look,
你刚才说有一成的几率幸存
you said ten percent would survive.
现在假如病毒变异过
Now, if the virus was altered,
有没有可能会提高存活率?
is there a chance the percentage would go up?
有可能 托尼
It's possible, Tony.
我们会尽一切努力救她
We'll do everything we can for her.
好 谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
整层楼?
The whole floor?
百万分之三十
30 parts per million.
服务区有没有检查过?
Have you check the service areas?
没 我正检查走廊
No, I have the corridor.
楼梯间
Stairwell.
-哪一层?  -所有
-Which floor?  -All levels.
百万分之三十五
35 parts per million.
电梯间
Elevator shaft.
我得到了不一致的数据
I am getting inconsistent readings on that.
好 再检查一遍 再向我报告
Ok, well, recheck it and get back to me.
收到
Copy that.
好
Ok, out.
一楼到五楼的浓度在百万分之三十以上
Floors one through five show 30 parts per million or greater.
和酒店其他地方一样 连大厅也被污染了
Yeah, same as the rest of the hotel. Even the lobby's contaminated.
好吧
Ok.
我联系反恐组 你联系卫生部
I will call CTU. You call NHS.
好
All right.
反恐组 科佩尔
CTU, Koppel.
-你好?  -我过会打给你
-Hello?  -I'll call you back.
盖尔.
Gael
米歇尔 别过来
Michelle, stay back.
我的一个同事刚出现病征
One of my agents just started showing symptoms.
到底怎么回事?
What the hell is going on?
这有关系吗?
Does that really matter?
潜伏期本该有14个小时的
The incubation period is supposed to be 14 hours,
你是他们的化学专家 你干了些什么?
you are the chemist, what did you do?
告诉我
Tell me.
我有个条件
Under one condition.
你现在没资格谈条件
You're in on position to be making demands.
我是唯一知情的人
I am the only one who knows what I did.
我会让它烂在我肚子里 除非你满足我的要求
And that dies with me, unless you do what I want.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
我了解那病毒
I know what the virus does.
我不想象那样死去
I don't want to die like that.
我会告诉你想要的
I will tell you what you want to know
只要你答应 一旦我出现症状马上杀了我
if you swear you will kill me once the symptoms start.
进来
Come
酒店的情况怎么样了?
What's the latest on the hotel?
还不清楚病毒的数量 和接触过的人数
It still unclear how much of that virus was released or how many people were exposed.
我觉得你应该准备发表如何应付病毒爆发的声明
Now I think you might want to make an announcement as to how to deal with the outbreak.
不 在弄清楚情况前 我不会作任何声明
No. I am not making any announcements until more facts are known.
听着 大卫 我刚从洛杉矶警局得到消息
Listen, David, I just heard from LAPD.
他们认为雪莉涉嫌谋杀
They consider Sherry to be a flight risk.
现在 大卫 他们要逮捕她
Now, David, they have a warrant for her arrest
如果你不帮她证明米利肯死的时候 你们在一起的话
if you don't back her alibi that she was with you when Milliken died.
你要我撒谎
You mean lie.
现在管不了这么多了
There is nothing to think about here.
连作伪证和妨碍司法公正都不在乎?
Perjury and obstruction of justice are nothing to think about?
大卫 这个世界上最强大的法律武器都归你支配
David, you have the most powerful legal apparatus in the world at your disposal.
你只要授命我给司法部长打个电话 所有问题就烟消云散
Now, you let me call the AG's office and this so called problem disappears.
不 不 不 这只会越陷越深 纸是包不住火的
No, no, no. It just widens the conspiracy, and it'll never hold.
你想让你苦心经营的一切毁于一旦?
Are you gonna let everything you have accomplished and I do mean everything be destroyed because of, what?
仅仅因为雪莉的无心之失?
because of... what, because of Sherry's indiscretion?
你知不知道自己在说什么 韦恩 你把谋杀叫无心之失?
Listen to yourself, Wayne, you are calling murder an indiscretion?
哦 看在上帝的份上 清醒点吧
Oh, for God's sakes, grow up.
你以为你在何谁说话?
Who the hell do you think you are talking to?
一个快下台的总统 大卫
To an ex-president, David,
除非你现在能做唯一有意义的事
unless you do the only thing that makes sense here.
雪莉说如果她栽了也要拉上你垫背
Now, Sherry said if she goes down, she's gonna take you down with her.
那就尽你所能阻止确保那不会发生
Then do your job and make sure that doesn't happen.
那就别让我束手束脚
Then stop tying my hands.
我要见警察局长
I want to see the chief of police.
该死 大卫 我们可以阻止这一切 我们能躲过一劫
Damn it, David, we can stonewall. We can survive this.
叫醒他 直接带他来见我
Get him out of bed and bring him directly to me.
怎么样了?
So where are we?
卡尔特兰 刚在离酒店两个街区的位置掉头
Caltrans just redirected all the traffic within a two block radius of the hotel.
克萝伊 我们的人还要多久能赶到?
Chloe, how long before we have enough agents around the hotel to keep everybody in?
大约还要半小时
We are at least a half hour away.
该死
Damn it.
托尼 米歇尔在3号线
Tony, I have got Michelle on line three.
好 我在那边接
All right, I willl take it over here.
嘿
Hey.
情况比我们想的糟糕
The situation is worse than we thought.
怎么了?
What are you talking about?
盖尔感染病毒不到一个小时就已经出现鼻口出血的症状了
Gael has started hemorrhaging from the nose and mouth less than an hour after exposure.
这么说病毒潜伏期不到14小时
So the incubation period is no longer 14 hours.
据阿尔弗斯所说与病毒结合的化学物质是起加速作用的
According to Alvers, the compound had added to the virus acts as an accelerant.
盖尔是唯一一个出现症状的?
Is Gael the only one showing symptoms?
据我所知是的
As far as I know.
他人在哪?
Where is he?
我把他隔离在一间地下室内
I isolated him in a room in the basement.
你有没有接触到他的血?
Were you exposed to any of his blood?
没有
No.
但我们检测了整个酒店的空气
But we've tested the air throughout the hotel.
病毒已经无处不在了 我也摄入了
The virus is everywhere and I have been breathing it.
听着 援军就快赶到了
All right, look, reinforcements are on their way.
我们得尽快建立强制隔离区
Everyone knows we need a hard perimeter as soon as possible.
我过会打给你
I will get back to you.
米歇尔
Michelle
现在没工夫谈别的了
We can't do this now.
我们必须确保没人离开这里
We have to focus on making sure no one gets out of here.
那好吧
Yeah. Ok.
菲利普斯先生 你得告诉我发生什么了
Mr. Phillips, you gotta tell me what's going on.
你在说什么 布鲁斯?
What are you talking about, Bruce?
别说你不知道
Don't' say you don't know.
酒店外到处是荷枪实弹的人 每个出口都被封锁了
There are people outside this hotel with guns, and every door I have tried is locked.
他们是联邦探员 他们在执行公务
They are federal agents, and they are dealing with a problem.
出了什么事?
What kind of problem?
我们有麻烦了吗? 告诉我
Are we in trouble? Please.
我知道的就这些了
The only thing I can tell you is all they have told me.
其他的我一无所知
I don't know any more.
那你就待在这无动于衷?
And you are sticking around?
我们别无选择
Look, we don't have a choice.
他们有权把我们限制在这
They have the authority to keep us here.
那我们该怎么办?
So what are we supposed to do?
在他们向我们透露更多消息之前 我们能做的就是保持冷静 期待一切会好起来
All we can do until they tell us more is to stay calm, and hope for the best,
好吗?
Ok?
好吧
Yeah
是我
我是米歇尔 你怎么样了?
It's Michelle. How are you feeling?
还好.
Ok, all right.
出血时断时续
The bleeding stops and starts.
我感到很虚弱
But I just feel very very weak.
卫生署的人一到 就会给你安排个医生
As soon as NHS gets here, they have gonna send a doctor in to see you.
还是先关注病毒的进展吧
To track the progress of the virus.
让你感觉好点
And to make you more comfortable.
你得让他们抓紧时间
You have gotta get them here soon.
当人们醒悟过来 把他们控制在酒店内就不是那么容易的事了
You are gonna have a had time keeping people in the hotel once they wake up.
怎么了 米歇尔?
What's that, Michelle?
我待会打给你
I will call you back.
我以为消防警报已经切断了
I thought the fire alarm was disconnected.
我也这么认为
I thought so, too.
能关掉吗?
Well, can you shut it off?
能 我正在想办法 我得找到手控装置
Yeah, I am on my way. I have to find the override.
打开广播 告诉人们是个误会 都呆在自己房间里
Get on the intercom. Tell people it was a false alarm and to stay in their rooms.
你们两个 去楼梯间把人挡回去
The two of you, I need you to go to the stairwell and turn people back around.
其他人 守住出口
Everyone else, man the doors.
一个人也不准出去
Nobody gets out.
我已经来回了好几趟 没人跟在我后面
Look, I have doubled back on my route a few times now, there is no one on my tail.
你肯定?
You're certain?
嗯 街上空荡荡的
Yes, the streets are empty.
快来见面
Just bring me in.
你离接头地点还有多远?
How far are you from the location?
不远了
I will be there soon.
把车停远一点走过来 找一辆银色的福特车
Park a few blocks away and walk. Look for a silver Ford.
我已经吩咐他带上你需要的证件
I told him we'll be waiting with your travel documents.
听着 我远走高飞还需要些钱
Look, I will need some cash to help me get out of the country.
也准备好了
He will have that for you as well.
好的
Good.
阿马多尔正在掉头 他往市区开了
Amador's making a UTurn. He is heading downtown.
好的 我们发现他了
Ok, we've got him.
通知增援部队
Bring in the follow teams.
告诉他们保持距离 除非他认为绝对安全
Tell them to stay at a safe distance. Amador's not going to lead us
否则阿马多尔不会领着我们去见他的老板
to who he is working for unless he feels absolutely safe.
立刻联系增援部队
Coordinating the follow teams now.
收到
Copy.
你那里情况怎样?
What's your status?
地下通道正常
The lower level is all clear.
坚守岗位
So hold your position.
收到
Copy that.
这是个误报警 大家都回到自己房间去
It was a false alarm, you all go back to your rooms.
所有人都会没事的
Everything will be ok.
我解除了警报 但系统需要缓冲
I deactivated the alarm node, but the system still has to cycle down.
需要多久?
Well, how long is it going to take?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想知道到底怎么了
I just want to know what the hell is going on.
别紧张 先生 一切正常
Take it easy, Sir. Everything is fine.
你需要放松点
You just need to relax.
可看起来并不好 不是吗?
Well, everything doesn't seem fine, ok?
只是警铃误响 没什么问题
It was a false alarm, it's no problem.
那为什么这些人告诉我不准出去
Then why is this guy telling me I can't run outside.
先生 请你回到楼上去
Please, Sir, I just need you to go upstairs.
不 除非有人告诉我发生了什么
No, not until someone tells me what is going on.
对
That's right.
为什么外面有那么多人? 我从房间里看到的
What are those people doing outside? I saw them from my room.
他们带着防毒面具
They are wearing gas masks.
你不能把我们关在这 我需要个合理解释
You can't keep us in here. I want an explanation.
请大家注意 我来解释一下情况
Please, please, if I can have your attention, I will explain the situation.
我是一名联邦探员 我之所以出现在这里是因为约半小时前
I am a federal agent. I am here because about half an hour ago,
有人在酒店外面释放了有毒物质
a toxic substance was released outside, around this building.
那为什么不早点告诉我们?
Why didn't you tell us that before?
因为我们不想引发慌乱
Because we didn't want people to panic and rush outside and
擅自出去会接触到这些危险物质
expose themselves to this dangerous substance.
现在 只要待在酒店里就是安全的
Now, you are safe as long as you stay inside this hotel,
但在消毒人员到来之前 外面是不安全的
but until we get a cleanup crew out there, it's not safe to go outside.
那我们要在这待多久?
Well, how long are we going to be here?
为什么电话打不了?
Why don't the phones work?
一切都会解决的 我保证
Please, please, we will work this all out, I promise you.
回到自己的房间里 所有人都会没事的
If you go back to your rooms, everything will be ok.
打扰一下 德斯勒探员 有人打开了防火门
Excuse me, Agent Dessler, someone got a fire door open.
哪里?
Where?
信号显示在酒店西侧
Signal came from the west side of the hotel.
所有的紧急通道都连着同一个走廊
All those emergency exits feed the same corridor.
好 你留在这里帮忙
All right, I need you to stay here and help my people out.
怎么过去?
How do I get there?
沿这条走廊右转 下楼就是
Down this corridor to the right, and downstairs.
好了 各位 回到自己房间去吧
All right, people, let's head back up to your rooms.
你们也听到了 没有大碍的
You heard the lady. There is no problem.
真是见鬼
Yeah, like hell there isn't.
请大家配合 一切都会好起来
Please. Everyone, it's gonna be just fine.
女士 请回到你房间去
Please, please, Ma'am, back to your room.
请大家配合 一切都会好起来
Please, everyone, it's gonna be just fine.
住手
Stop right there.
我要离开这
I am getting out of here.
我是联邦探员
I am a federal agent.
把枪放下
Now, drop the gun.
不 我只想离开
No. I just want to go.
离开这里不安全
It's not safe to leave.
把枪放下
Drop the gun.
为什么不安全?
Why isn't it safe?
酒店外面被释放了有毒物质
A toxic substance was released outside around this hotel.
你撒谎
You are lying.
不 我没有
No, I am not lying.
不 我看到了储藏室那个男人
No. I know about the man in the storeroom.
我知道酒店里肯定出事了
I know that something bad is in this hotel.
对 是这样
You are right. It is.
正因为此 你更不能离开
That's why you can't go outside.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
酒店里的所有人都会病的很严重
Everyone in this hotel is going to get very sick.
病? 多严重?
Sick? How sick?
大部分人会死去
Most of us are going to die.
不可能
That's not possible.
是真的
It's the truth.
我要回家见我妻子
I just want to get home to my wife.
我妻子
My wife.
如果你去了 你也会传染给他
If you do, you will give this to her.
任何人离开酒店 疾病就会传播
Anyone who leaves this hotel, will spread this disease.
上万人会被死去
Tens of thousands of people could die.
你也不想成这个元凶 对吗?
You don't want to be responsible for that, do you?
哦 天哪
Oh, God.
把枪给我
Give me the gun.
现在你也知道了 我们得把你隔离起来
Now that you know, we have to isolate you.
坐下
Sit down.
我是德斯勒
Dessler.
你得回来 这里有情况
We need you back in here. There is a problem.
怎么了?
What's going on?
有人开始鼻口出血
Someone just started bleeding from the nose and mouth.
血流不止
The blood keeps coming and we can't stop it.
总统先生
Mr. President.
亨德里克斯局长来了
Chief Hendricks.
局长
Chief.
总统先生
Mr. President.
请坐
Please have a seat.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
我知道现在会见并不合适
I realize this is an irregular hour for a meeting.
情况特殊 总统先生
The circumstances are irregular, Mr President.
确实
Yes, they are.
我猜你已经接手了米利肯的案子
I assume you have been briefed on the Milliken case.
我知道朱莉娅 米利肯指认帕默尔夫人
I know Julia Milliken stated that Mrs Palmer contributed to the death of
扣下了艾伦·米利肯的药 导致他死亡
Alan Milliken by withholding his medication.
帕默尔夫人对我们说当晚
Mrs Palmer indicated to our detectives that she was not
她不在米利肯的住处 她和您在一起
at Milliken residence this evening, that she was here with you.
总统先生 我想知道 这是真的吗?
Mr. President, my question is: was she?
是 没错
Yes, she was.
谢谢您 总统先生
Thank you, Mr President.
谢谢你 亨德里克斯局长
Thank you, Chief Hendricks.
祝你晚安
Have a good night.
谢谢您 先生
Thank you, sir.
你觉得米利肯夫人会出于什么动机控告帕默尔夫人?
Is there any reason you can think of that would have prompted Mrs Milliken to accuse Mrs Palmer?
狗急跳墙吧 局长
People do inexplicable things in a moment of crisis, Chief.
嗯
Yeah.
晚安
Good night.
警察局长刚来过
The police chief was just here.
我告诉他当晚你和我在一起
And I told him that you were here with me tonight.
没人会怀疑
And no one will ever know anything different.
我会
I will.
你犯下不可饶恕的罪孽
What you have done is unforgivable.
大卫 你打电话给我是因为你需要有人帮你做这种见不得人的事
David, you called me precisely because you needed someone to do your dirty work.
所以别以为你能跟这一切划清界限
So don't turn around and just try to wash your hands of this.
你怎么敢含血喷人
Don't you dare insinuate that I knew what you were about to do.
你夺走了一条生命
You took a life.
大卫 你逃不了干系
It's not that clear cut, David.
不
Yes, it is.
艾伦·米利肯是你害死的
Alan Milliken is dead because of you.
你需要人帮你解决米利肯 我替你办了
You needed help with Milliken, and I gave it to you.
我们都没想到会搞成这样
Neither of us had any idea that it would work out like this.
但别忘了 这的确帮了你的忙
So let's not forget, it did work out in your favor.
你应该感谢我
You should be thanking me.
我为你的所作所为感到羞耻
I despise you for what you have done.
我也鄙视我自己还帮你开脱
And I despise my role in helping you get away with it.
再也别出现在我面前了
Now get out of my sight.
好 我发现他了
Ok, I have got him.
增援部队已经就位了吗?
Are the following cars in place?
是的 长官
Affirmative, sir.
增援已就位
We have the pursuing cars in position.
这是你要的钱和护照
Here is your money and travel paper.
快
Move.
该死的
Damn it.
你去用无线电通知
You get on the radio.
告诉支援部队封锁整个区域
You tell the follow teams to cordon off this entire area.
在排爆组和现场勘查组到来之前 别让任何人靠近这里
I don't want anybody coming down here except for the bomb squad and forensics.
我们需要封锁这两个街区...
Two block perimeter around...
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
你好 杰克
Hello Jack.
我知道你比阿马多尔技高一筹...
I knew you were better than Amador. but...
但不见得比我强
you are not better than me.
阿马多尔说你认识我
Amador said you knew me.
你是谁?
Who is this?
当务之急 杰克
First thing first, Jack.
还有11管病毒
There are 11 other vials,
和在酒店里放出的那管一样
each containing the same amount of virus that was released at the hotel.
要是不接受我的要求 我会继续释放
I will use them the moment my instructions aren't followed.
你要什么 钱?
What do you want, money?
我要你帮我联系你的一个朋友
I need you to put me in touch with a friend of yours.
这一切就会烟消云散
Everything is going to be ok.
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
先生 叫菲利普斯来 不会有事的
Sir.I need phillips,it will be ok.
他们骗了我们
They are lying to us.
是酒店里面出了问题
There is something wrong inside the building.
是酒店里面
It's inside the building.
先生 请冷静 所有人 听我的
sir,clam down.everyone,on my way.
不要靠近大门 回来
Keep away from the doors. Stay back.
不许动
Hold it right there.
离窗户远点
Step away from the window.
我说了离那窗户远点
I said step away from the window.
如果你再试图离开 我会开枪的
If you try to leave, I will shoot you.
不 你不会的
No, you won't.
总统先生 杰克·鲍尔的电话
Mr President, I have Jack Bauer for you.
谢谢
Thank you
杰克
Jack
总统先生 持有科迪利亚病毒的人想和您谈谈
Mr President, the man in possession of the Cordilla virus has demanded to speak with you.
我们还不知道他是谁 先生
We don't have a name on him yet, sir.
但我确信如果你拒绝和他交谈 他会释放更多病毒
But I do believe that if you don't speak with him, he'll release more of the virus.
非常不幸 总统先生
Unfortunately, Mr President, right now at this time
现在这情况你只能向他妥协
I think you are going to have to give in to this demands.
我和他谈谈
I will speak to him.
好 我帮你接通他
Yes, sir, I will connect you.
已经接通总统
You're on with President.
我长话短说
I'll make this brief.
相信你已经意识到 我手上有足够的病毒
As you are no doubt aware, I am in possession of enough of the virus
能杀死一大批人
to decimate a good portion of the population of this country.
就像我在钱德勒 广场酒店展示的一样
And as I have shown at the Chandler Plaza Hotel,
我会故技重施
I will do so unless you follow the instructions.
除非你按照接下来几个小时内我的指示去做
You will be receiving over the next few hours.
明白了吗 总统先生?
Do you understand, Mr President?
我在听着
I am listening.
你已无力控制你的国家
You are no longer in control of your country,
如果你不动用你的权利来满足我的要求
and if you do not use the full power of your office to execute my wishes,
我会继续释放病毒 一切将无法控制
the virus will be released, and it will be impossible to stop.
我过会再打给你
You will be hearing from me.